# Gary Yu

Authorized to work in the U.S. 1436 Wolfberry Ln, Northlake, TX 76262

# **SUMMARY**

5+ years of experience in supply chain and logistics, including 2 years of management position in automotive industry. Skilled at Process Improvement (Lean & Six Sigma), Supply Chain Management, Production Control & Planning, Customer Relations and Safety & Compliance, with knowledge of Python, SQL, Microsoft Office, and ERP. Fluent in English, Chinese, Taiwanese.

## **EDUCATION**

# Master of Engineering, Industrial Engineering- Engineering management

Jan.2019-Dec.2019

Email: garyyu@buffalo.edu Cell: (940) 784-3469

State University of New York at Buffalo

Buffalo, New York

Relevant Courses: Engineering Management, Production Planning and Control, Facility Design, Quality Assurance, Supply Chain Management, Programming and Database Fundamentals, Lean Enterprise.

#### Certificate- Automotive Technology

Jan. 2015-May. 2016

Jefferson Community and Technical College

Louisville, Kentucky

#### Bachelor of Business in Finance

Sep. 2009-Jul. 2013

National Taichung University of Science and Technology

Taichung, Taiwan

## **EXPERIENCE**

# Logistic Supervisor/Material planner - Macauto USA Inc.

Feb.2017-Oct. 2018

Rochester, New York

- Improved the receiving and shipping processes by redesigning the procedure
- Modified NAFTA documentation to fulfill the requirement
- Negotiated and came to an agreement with suppliers with a lower price for raw materials
- Improved Supplier delivery rating score from 82 to 98 Ford super-G Rating
- Solved the warehouse space issue by outsourcing partial of goods to the qualified, and reliable 3<sup>rd</sup> party and analyzing the obsolete goods
- Increased inventory accuracy from 88% to 100% by process redesign
- Increased 22% of the productivity of sorting and reworking line by addressing bottlenecks and adjusting gauges, and jig
- Managed 5 to 20 employees for daily operating, sorting, and re-working activities (seasonal adjusted)
- Day-to-day domestic and internal logistics activities for OEM and tier 1 customers
- Assisted company to renew the ISO/IATF 16949 certificate
- Lowered inventory level without causing shortage issues

# **Inventory Coordinator – Legend Lumber Corp,**

Jun. 2016-Jan.2017

Boston, Kentucky

- Set up and maintained the inventory system with zero discrepancy
- Arranged and scheduled incoming and outgoing truckload to achieve delivery on-time
- Design the templates of invoice, PO and documents for international shipping

### Assistant Supervisor – Capatina Inc.

Sep. 2006-Aug. 2009

Taipei, Taiwan

- Arranged monthly workforce schedule to satisfy all the labor need for every branch
- Supervised monthly cycle count to validate the system discrepancy
- Arranged delivery route